Aah! Tiny Spock! Help!
- Ready for lunch?
- Yeah, one sec. Ahh.
Oh, good. Ma would've killed me
if she found out I broke my retainer.
(Raj:)Hey, uh, can I run something by you?
It's about Lakshmi.
(Howard:)Yeah, sure. How are things going?
(Raj:)We hit a couple of bumps.
She lives over in Manhattan Beach,
so it takes like an hour to get there.
(Raj:)And she's a lesbian.
What do you mean, a lesbian?
Well, you know whenever you and l
would try to hit on women in bars...
(Raj:)...they'd blow us off,
then we'd tell each other they were gay?
(Raj:)It's like that.
(Raj:)Except this time, it's true.
(Howard:)- Why did she even go out with you?
- She was looking for a husband...
(Raj:)...so she can appear to be straight.
(Raj:)And, you know,
it sounded crazy to me at first...
(Raj:)...but I'm actually thinking about doing it.